# GISELE ATADAIME

TESTER AND TEST AUTOMATION DEVELOPER

### CONTACT

SOROCABA, SP. BRAZIL

+55 15 99653-3401

GISELETAMIE@HOTMAIL.COM

GISELEATADAIME.GITHUB.IO

GITHUB.COM/GISELEATADAIME

# PROFILE

**LINKEDIN** 

I am a professional based in Brazil. Experienced Automation Test Analyst with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry.

Skilled in Java, manual testing, test automation and Agile Methodologies.

## SKILLS

- Java
- Selenium
- TestNG
- Agile methodologies
- JavaScript
- Git and gitflow
- Docker
- SQL and PL/SQL
- MS Office
- Test automation

### LANGUAGES

- Portuguese Fluent
- English Advanced
- Japanese Beginner

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# TESTER AND TEST AUTOMATION DEVELOPER FOR WEB APPLICATIONS

IBM | JAN 2020 - CURRENT

- Work in Scrum agile team
- Black box testing
- Development of Automated Regression Tests
- Documenting Test Cases
- Report and documenting bugs
- Also developed some React JS Interfaces for internal tasks

#### **IT INTERN**

IBM | MAY 2019 - DEC 2019

- Application development with Java;
- Test execution for change requirements and defects approvals;
- Test scripts for test documentation;
- Regression tests black box type;
- RPA of repetitive test tasks, like regression test, using java + Selenium.

#### **IT INTERN**

GRUPO SOROCRED | MAR 2018 - APR 2019

- Support to the organization's internal systems;
- Analyze and code bug fixes of source code in PL/SQL;
- Shell script coding for file receiving automation;
- SQL queries writing for on demand custom reports;

### **EDUCATION**

UNDERGRADUATE - SYSTEM ANALYSIS AND DEVELOPMENT FACULDADE DE TECNOLOGIA DE SOROCABA 2016-2019

### AWARDS

### IBM ASSOCIATES ROCKSTAR 2021 1Q

Nominated as rockstar amongst associates for accomplishments within internal project, based on leadership, innovation and impact to clients.